International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Southington Lodge 1746A Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Office Files, 1970-1983
  - Terminations, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 329)
  - Thank-you letters and cards, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 330)
  - United Way, 1977 (Box 6:, Folder 331)
  - A. Philip Randolf Institute, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 332)
  - Alcoholism, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 333)
  - Applications: returned from company, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 334)
  - Cash members list, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 335)
  - Change of status, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 336)
  - Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 337)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 338)
  - Correspondence, Lodge 1746A, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 339)
  - DelGiudice, Marea: Recording Secretary, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 340)
  - District 91, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 341)
  - Dropout list, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 342)
  - Grand Lodge, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 343)
  - Greater Bristol Labor Council, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 344)
  - Greater Meriden Labor Council, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 345)
  - IAM Electronic Conference, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 346)
  - Iaccio, Sal: General Vice President, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 347)
  - Local View: Editors and Public Relations, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 348)
  - Machinist Non-Partisan Political League, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 349)
  - New England Conference, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 350-351)
  - New member lists, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 352)
  - Peretta, James, 1978
    - Personnel Supervisory, excludes letters (Box 6:, Folder 353)
    - Correspondence (Box 6:, Folder 354-356)
  - Population by shift, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 357)
  - Put ons, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 358)
  - Quarterly configurations, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 359)
  - Softball league, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 360)
  - Steward roster changes, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 361)
  - Terminations, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 362)
  - Tinella, Joseph: President, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 363)
  - Union articles for newsletter publication, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 364)
  - United Way, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 365)
  - Wipsinger, William: International President, 1978 (Box 6:, Folder 366)
  - Change of status, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 367)
  - Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 368)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 369-370)
  - Counselors Information, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 371)
  - DelGiudice, Marea: Recording Secretary, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 372)
  - District 91, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 373)
  - Dungan, Roy: recreation, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 374)
  - Election rules, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 375)
  - Financial reports, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 376)
  - Greater Bristol Labor Council, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 377)
  - Greater Meriden Labor Council, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 378)
  - Hitchery, Regina: Personnel Supervisory, Payroll deductions, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 379)
  - IAM correspondence, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 380)
  - Labor Education, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 381)
  - Machinist Non-Partisan Political League, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 382)
  - Material shortage, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 383)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 384)
  - New England Conference, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 385-386)
  - Paper clippings, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 387)
  - Peretta, James, 1978
    - Personnel Supervisory, excludes letters (Box 7:, Folder 388)
    - Correspondence (Box 7:, Folder 389-390)
  - Population by shift, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 391)
  - Pratt and Whitney: correspondence, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 392)
  - Pratt and Whitney: sales reports, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 393)
  - Put ons, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 394)
  - Safety Commission, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 395)
  - Shea, Thomas: correspondence, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 396)
  - Smith, Floyd, International President: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 397)
  - Steward's information, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 398)
  - Steward's roster changes, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 399)
  - Terminations, 1978 (Box 7:, Folder 400)
  - United Technologies sales report, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 401)
  - Weighted average hourly wage, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 402)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 403)
  - Paper clippings and notes, 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 404)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission concerning General Electric, 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 405)
  - Wages/Cost of living allowance, 1980 (Box 7:, Folder 406)
  - Pratt and Whitney Personnel Report, 1981 (Box 7:, Folder 407)
  - United Technologies Annual Report, 1981 (Box 7:, Folder 408)
  - Aerospace Report, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 409)
  - Committee members, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 410)
  - Economics of divestments, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 411)
  - Industry overview, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 412)
  - Negotiations, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 413)
  - Personnel notes, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 414)
  - Press, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 415)
  - United Technologies Annual Report, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 416)
  - Negotiations and agreements, 1982 (Box 7:, Folder 417-418)
  - Committee members: delegates, 1983 (Box 7:, Folder 419)
- Series IV: Publications, 1970-1982
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1970 (Box 8:, Folder 420)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 421)
  - Lodge 1746A miscellaneous notices, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 422)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1972 (Box 8:, Folder 423)
  - Connecticut AFL-CIO Call to Action, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 424)
  - IAM official circulars, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 425)
  - Pratt and Whitney Power Plant, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 426)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 427)
  - IAM District 91 general bulletins, 1974 (Box 8:, Folder 428-430)
  - IAM official circulars, 1974 (Box 8:, Folder 431)
  - IAM The Machinist, 1974 (Box 8:, Folder 432-434)
  - IAM District 91 pamphlets, 1974 (Box 8:, Folder 435)
  - Pratt and Whitney Power Plant, 1974 (Box 8:, Folder 436)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1974 (Box 8:, Folder 437)
  - United Aircraft Beehive, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 438)
  - IAM Lodge 971 Florida Labor News, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 439)
  - IAM District 91 general bulletins, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 440)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council Legislative Bulletin, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 441)
    - IAM The Machinist, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 442-443)
  - Various sources, miscellaneous notices, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 444)
  - IAM District 91 New Union News, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 445)
  - Pratt and Whitney Power Plant, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 446)
  - Palm Beach Country Federation of Labor Palm Beach County Labor News, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 447)
  - Pratt and Whitney 50th Anniversary, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 448)
  - Pratt and Whitney Power Plant, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 449)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1975 (Box 8:, Folder 450)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council Legislative Bulletin, 1976 (Box 8:, Folder 451)
  - IAM The Machinist, 1976 (Box 8:, Folder 452-453)
  - Pratt & Whitney Power Plant, 1976 (Box 8:, Folder 454)
  - IAM District 91 Shop Talk, 1976 (Box 8:, Folder 455)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1976 (Box 8:, Folder 456)
  - IAM bargaining survey, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 457)
  - IAM District 91 general bulletins, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 458-459)
  - IAM The Machinist, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 460-461)
  - Various sources, miscellaneous notices, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 462)
  - IAM District 91 Shop Talk, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 463)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 464)
  - Various sources, campaign flyers, and originals, 1978 (Box 9:, Folder 465)
  - IAM District 91 general bulletins, 1978 (Box 9:, Folder 466)
  - IAM The Machinist, 1978 (Box 9:, Folder 467-468)
  - IAM District 91 Shop Talk, 1978 (Box 9:, Folder 469)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1978 (Box 9:, Folder 470)
  - Connecticut State Labor Council AFL-CIO News, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 471)
  - AFL-CIO Bulletin # 22, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 472)
  - AFL-CIO The Builders, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 473)
  - Connecticut Citizen-Labor Energy Coalition materials, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 474)
  - IAM circulars, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 475)
  - IAM Keeping in Touch, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 476)
  - AFL-CIO Labaletter, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 477)
  - IAM The Machinist, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 478)
  - AFL-CIO Memo from COPE (Committee on Political Education) and Legislative Alert, 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 479)
  - Various sources, miscellaneous notices, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 480)
  - IAM Report from Headquarters, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 481)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 482)
  - International Metal Workers Trade Unions and Collective Bargaining in the Aerospace Industry, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder I483)
  - International Metal Workers Aerospace Company Profiles Co-Production, and Company Profiles, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 484)
  - Lodge 1746A Union Bulletin, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 485)
  - IAM Report from Headquarters, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 486)
  - IAM District 91 Shop Talk, 1980 (Box 10:, Folder 487)
  - Various sources, miscellaneous notices, 1981 (Box 10:, Folder 488)
  - IAM District 91 Shop Talk, 1981 (Box 10:, Folder 489)
  - IAM; AFL-CIO Electrical Union News, 1982 (Box 10:, Folder 490)
- Series V: Personnel Evaluations **RESTRICTED**
- Series VI: Grievances **RESTRICTED**